Hey cozy gamers, Restory chill
electronics repairs [music] is finally
out and with a game that has boasted
over 600,000 wish list, there are going
to be a lot of players diving into this
game. If you're unaware, Restory is a
story driven shop management simulator
set in mid-2000s Tokyo where you take
over a repair shop after the previous
master has gone [music] missing. Not
only are you taking over a legacy, but
you're falling into a situation that
isn't exactly the best. You'll notice
some characters are more rough around
the edges and find yourself with choices
that could lead you down paths that may
or may not be the best outcome for you
or the other characters involved. While
this video isn't here to help guide you
down the branching dialogue paths that
you could come across, it does have 20
tips and tricks I wish I knew before
playing Restory. So, let's go ahead and
talk about them. When playing the game,
there are several upgrades that you
could grab and honestly, you can skip
buying the can of air. It'll only last
for a little while and the brush
upgrades are cheap. Prioritize upgrading
those for an easier time dislodging
dust.
The screwdriver is probably the most
helpful upgrade and I'd recommend
prioritizing it.
>> [music]
>> It only has two upgrades and the last
one instantly handles the screws, which
is so, so handy. [music]
The tip jar is invaluable. Even though
it's a physical jar at your store,
you'll get tips on both walk-up and
online orders. Each completed job will
reward you with an extra 200 to 500 yen
and that really stacks up over time.
In the beginning, broken parts go
straight into the trash. By grabbing the
shredder, you'll see a return on each
part you shred of about 200 to 500 yen.
This will add up over time because there
are a lot of things that come in [music]
that are broken.
When pulling items apart, I found it
helpful to put the dirty items on one
side and the clean items on the other so
that I could easily find what needed to
be cleaned. The notepad will tell you
what's clean and highlight it, but it's
easier when things are separated and you
can just grab them on muscle memory
alone.
If you get turned around when trying to
put something back [music] together, you
can check your notepad. Not only will it
tell you that what items are broken,
missing, or need to be cleaned, but it's
in the order that things need to be put
back together in. When you're pulling
things apart, it's easy to think that
you'll remember in what order they go
in, but I can't tell you how many times
I got lost. So, it's really helpful to
have on the side. You can buy a sonic
bath, but it's useless in the beginning.
It allows you to put three items into
it, but it takes 30 seconds to clean
them, and you're usually sitting around
waiting for it. For the cost, it's not
worth it until mid to late gameplay,
[music]
and it's only worth it if you can
continue through to the next sonic bath
upgrades, which will allow you to do
even more items at a time for less
[music] time. The only time it's really
helpful is if the dirty items are at the
beginning of the things you're taking
apart. Otherwise, if it's at the last
bit, you're just going to sit there and
wait, and it's not worth it.
Early on, you'll be asked to pick an
internet plan. There's a 500, 1,000,
[music] and 1,500 yen plan. As of right
now, they don't really matter, but in
the discussions on Steam, the devs have
indicated that it may affect the game
later. [music]
You make enough money to buy the largest
plan, so go ahead and get the 1,500 yen
plan. It may not end up mattering in the
end, but I promise you that you won't
miss that extra 1,000 yen. Also early
on, you'll need to buy electronics off
the market and pull them apart for spare
parts. You won't know the condition of
the item until you get your hands on it.
There is a description and ratings, but
those don't always tell the truth. By
buying a license for that particular
electronic, you'll be able to buy new
parts straight from the source.
>> [music]
>> It's not guaranteed to be cheaper, but
you'll know for a fact that you're
getting the part that you need. The
market has spare part boxes that are
small, medium, and large. Buy them. You
won't know what's in them until they
arrive, but it's several parts for a
better price than buying parts or
electronics for parts.
>> [music]
>> I try to remember to look at the shop
every single day because you never know
when these boxes are going to drop. The
story only progresses through buying
licenses. Walk-up customers will
sometimes have items that you don't have
a license to fix. You'll still take the
item, but it'll just sit onto the side
and you won't be able to progress until
the item is fixed. So, if you're looking
to build up a little nest egg for
upgrades, you can continue fixing and
cleaning things in this time period
without worrying about missing out on
major story lines. You may be interested
in buying the airbrush upgrade that
allows you to paint your electronics,
but I'd ignore it unless you're
interested in drawing or a job requires
it because painting the item does not
increase its value. All you're doing is
kind of wasting time in the day, but
like I said, if you're creative and you
want to make art, then absolutely go for
it. It just won't help you in the long
run as far as money goes.
Likewise, there's a toolkit upgrade that
allows you to reprogram electronics that
is overall useless. You'll need to play
a small mini-game where you constantly
tap the keys to fill up a bar until it's
successful, but it doesn't increase the
value of your item. I'd wait for it to
be required by a client because
otherwise it literally does nothing for
you and it's kind of expensive. Online
orders are something that you can count
on every single day. You'll always have
11 to choose from that are a mix of
items that just need to be cleaned or
ones that need repairs. You'll have 3
days to complete them, so be sure to
complete them within that time or it may
negatively impact the ratings you get
[music] from your customers. The shop
closes at midnight and you won't be able
to send or receive anything until 8:00
a.m. the next morning. [music]
I like to use this time to blaze through
the cleaning jobs since it doesn't
require any extra parts. It allows me to
have a stockpile of items that go out in
the morning for a nice hunk of cash to
start the day with.
>> [music]
>> While you can stay up through the night
and just continue to work from one day
to the next, the day won't change over
until you actually go home and sleep.
So, if you want to make sure your days
are counted properly, be sure to go home
before 8:00 a.m.
You'll have bills to pay every week, but
it's manageable.
>> [music]
>> You'll have rent and internet up front
and with story progression, you'll
eventually pay electricity and a
security bill. If you go for the highest
internet, your weekly cost will be 6,000
yen and 5,000 with the cheaper internet.
It's an easy amount to keep on hand, and
only rent and internet come in at the
[music] same time. So, you don't really
have to worry about your bills being
paid because you'll probably have that
on hand.
By going to the other tabs in the D Pop
store, you'll be able to buy accessories
for decorations, new shelving to hold
things, paint colors for your airbrush
machine, and stickers to decorate your
devices with. Again, these don't add
value to them, but they are fun, and if
you want to make your own individual
style, then I [music] recommend going
for it. Most characters you interact
with will have shady backstories. Your
choices will affect not only just your
interaction with them, but potentially
the outcome of their lives. So, be very
careful with the choices you make and be
certain [music]
because an innocent comment may back you
into a set of follow-up answers that may
force you to unintentionally snitch on
someone. Lastly, there is a character
Harahi who will offer to send over spare
parts she, quote unquote, comes across.
Initially, I told her no because I
wasn't sure that I wanted to deal with
questionably sourced parts. She'll later
send you an email where the offer still
stands. If you want to enjoy extra
parts, I'd go ahead and do it in this
[music] first conversation because I
eventually decided to accept her help,
and it's been several days with no
movement on that front. I don't know if
she only does this once a week or if
she's glitched, but if you want to get
in on early for the extra benefit, I'd
do that as soon as she offers it. Just
be aware that this may come with
negative consequences later. I'm several
hours into the game, and these were the
things that I wish I knew before diving
in. I spent a lot of money in needlessly
trying out upgrades that didn't serve me
because I just bought them too early. My
money would have been better spent on
licenses at that point. I hope this
guide helps you, and I'd love to know if
you enjoy playing Re Story as much as I
have. If you didn't know, I also have a
website that has the articles these
videos are adapted from that you can
take a glance at.
>> [music]
>> The links to it, my socials, and the
Comfy Cozy Gaming Discord server are all
linked in the description. Until [music]
next time, may your gaming sessions be
comfy and cozy. See you later.